(Instrument)
Watching the sun...watching it come
Watching it come up over the rooftops
Cloudy and warm...maybe a storm
You can never quite tell from the morning
And it's going to be a day
There is really no way to say no to the morning
Yes it's going to be a day
There is really nothing left to say but come on morning
(Instrument)
Waiting for mail Maybe a tale
from an old friend or even a lover
Sometimes there's none But we have fun
thinking of all who might have written
And it's going to be a day
There is really no way to say no to the morning
Yes it's going to be a day
There is really nothing left to say but come on morning
(Instrument)
And maybe there are seasons
And maybe they change
And maybe to love is not so strange
(Instrument)
Ooooooo......
The sounds of the day
Now they hurry away
Now they are gone until tomorrow
When day will break and you will wake
And you will rake your hands across your eyes and realize
That it's going to be a day
There is really no way to say no to the morning
Yes it's going to be a day
There is really nothing left to say but come on morning
(Instrument)
And maybe there are seasons
and maybe they change
And maybe to love is not so strange
(Music faded away...)