[Rock music]
I'm losing sight
Don't count on me
I chase the sun
It chases me
You know my name
You know my face
You'd know my heart
If you knew my place
I'll walk straight down
As far as I can go
I follow you
You follow me
I don't know why
You lie so clean
I'll break right through
The irony
Enlighten me
Reveal my fate
Just cut these strings
That hold me safe
You know my head
You know my gaze
You'd know my heart
If you knew your place
I'll walk straight down
As far as I can go
I follow you
You follow me
I don't know why
You lie so clean
I'll break right through the irony
Kill
This
Wait
I
I hate this wait
I follow you
You follow me
I don't know why, you lie so clean
I'll break right through the irony
I don't know why
I follow you, you follow me
I don't know why you lie so clean
I'll break right through the irony